worlddancesport.org 2011-12-27

# Privacy Policy | World DanceSport Federation at worlddancesport.org

## Information Collection and Use

Unless the user provides it voluntarily, the World DanceSport Federation (WDSF) does not collect any personally identifiable information about visitors to its website.

### E-Mail

Some pages permit visitors to request additional information. Visitors are able to e-mail messages to WDSF and/or its officials that will contain the user's name and e-mail address, as well as any additional information the user may wish to include in the message. WDSF uses the information visitors provide about themselves to fulfil those visitors' requests. In this case, the e-mail addresses are used to answer messages received only.

In order to be able to comment on the "Live from ..." blog entries - or to take part in surveys or polls on this website - a visitor is required to register and log in first ( **Login | Register** next to the **SEARCH** field). The mandatory fields for registration include

  * Name 
  * Surname 
  * User name (selected) 
  * Password 
  * Email 

The check box confirms acceptance of this Privacy Policy. 

### Newsletter

Under the terms of the Privacy Policy, all registrants sign up automatically for the monthly IDSF newsletter **To The Rhythm of Time (** TTROT) to be sent to them by e-mail.

While WDSF does not share any information it stores about the registrants with third parties, it makes use of Name, Surname and Email for the distribution of the monthly newsletter. The latter is distributed through ConstantContact, a reputable service for bulk mailing. Refer to the Constant Contact privacy statement [ here](http://www.constantcontact.com/privacy_guarantee.jsp "ConstantContact"). Should a registrant to the website prefer not to receive the newsletter TTROT, the instant removal function  in the footer of each issue allows for the automatic subscription to be cancelled at any time. 

### Log Files

We use IP addresses and we track navigation path to analyse trends and administer the site. These IP addresses and URLs are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Security

Given the nature of the Internet and the fact that no security system is perfect, WDSF cannot guarantee that the information you provide will never be obtained by an unauthorised person. WDSF does, however, utilise industry-standard practices to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration and destruction. Such measures include using security layers to protect certain sensitive transmissions of information.

### Privacy Policy Changes

The World DanceSport Federation reserves the right to change its privacy policy from time to time.
